{
  "title": "English -> Argentine Spanish [Intro course]",
  "emoji": "ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡·",
  "version": "pre0.1",
  "level_groups": [
    {
      "title": "Introduction",
      "tiles": [
        {
          "description": "ARGENTINE SPANISH (NOT SPAIN SPANISH)",
          "content": {
            "title": "The proper basics",
            "flashcards": [
              {
                "front": "Hello",
                "back": "Hola",
                "help": "Blud, you're cooked ðŸ’€"
              },
              {
                "front": "Goodbye",
                "back": "Chau"
              },
              {
                "front": "Please",
                "back": "Por fa'"
              },
              {
                "front": "I",
                "back": "Yo"
              },
              {
                "front": "You",
                "back": "Vos",
                "help": "It's NOT SPAIN SPANISH"
              },
              {
                "front": "He",
                "back": "Ã‰l"
              },
              {
                "front": "She",
                "back": "Ella"
              }
            ]
          }
        },
        {
          "description": "Learn basic flashcards",
          "content": {
            "title": "The basics pt.2",
            "flashcards": [
              {
                "front": "How are you",
                "back": "Â¿CÃ³mo te va?"
              },
              {
                "front": "Who",
                "back": "Â¿QuiÃ©n?"
              },
              {
                "front": "I am",
                "back": "Yo soy"
              },
              {
                "front": "You are",
                "back": "Vos sos"
              },
              {
                "front": "He/she is",
                "back": "Ã‰l/Ella es"
              }
            ]
          }
        },
        {
          "description": "Practice reading",
          "content": {
            "title": "Conversation with Rodrigo and Hugo",
            "sentences": [
              {
                "clauses": [
                  {
                    "original": "R -",
                    "translated": "R -"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "Hola",
                    "translated": "Hi"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "Â¿QuiÃ©n sos?",
                    "translated": "Who are you?"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "clauses": [
                  {
                    "original": "H -",
                    "translated": "H -"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "Soy Hugo,",
                    "translated": "I am Hugo,"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "Â¿y vos?",
                    "translated": "and you?"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "clauses": [
                  {
                    "original": "R -",
                    "translated": "R -"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "SÃ­,",
                    "translated": "Yes,"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "yo soy Rodrigo,",
                    "translated": "I am Rodrigo,"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "Â¿cÃ³mo te va?",
                    "translated": "how are you?"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "clauses": [
                  {
                    "original": "H -",
                    "translated": "H -"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "Re bien,",
                    "translated": "Really good,",
                    "help": "Re: really"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "Â¿y vos?",
                    "translated": "and you?"
                  }
                ]
              },
              {
                "clauses": [
                  {
                    "original": "R -",
                    "translated": "R -"
                  },
                  {
                    "original": "Â¡Tremendo!",
                    "translated": "Awesome!",
                    "help": "Tremendo: great"
                  }
                ]
              }
            ]
          }
        }
      ],
      "color": "--green"
    }
  ]
}
